# Blame Yang

Innovative Game Developer Proficient in Smart Contract Engineering Ontario, Canada

## **Summary**

Senior Unity and Smart Contract Developer with over 7+ years of experience in writing clean code which bring robust automation. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving satisfaction, and driving overall operational improvements. Consistently saved costs and time while increasing profits.

## **Experience**

Unity Developer - 03/2014 to 10/2019 Nintendo, Kyoto

- Expert with C# scripting in the Unity environment
- Strong knowledge of OOP, design patterns and data structures
- Excellent knowledge of Unity3D, including experience with scripting, materials/shaders, and Unity GUI
- Collaborating closely with artists and designers to build and iterate on prototypes to achieve a shared creative vision
- Strong experience shipping consumer products across several platforms
- Expert knowledge of Unity3D Pro including building asset bundles
- Assist in architecting a new game engine
- Participate in team meetings relating to designing system architecture

# Online Game Team Manager - 02/2020 to 4/2022 GhostShark Games, Rome

- Writing clean, readable and reusable code that is well documented
- Provides leadership in the professional practice setting and the profession
- API creation / management
- Use Online Game Server Engine such as SFS, Photon, KBEngine etc.
- Familiar with NFT Online Game development by Smart Contract and Web3
- Source code management in a collaborative environment
- Collaborating directly with external customers
- Managing the day-to-day operations of their team
- Quickly learn complex systems and new technologies

#### **Skills**

- Good verbal and written communication skills that are clear and professional
- Familiar with Complex and Comfortable Online Game Server Engines
- Experience with scripting, textures, animation, GUI styles, and game physics and particle systems in Unity
- Good knowledge of Block Chain and NFT gameplay programming
- Experience in delivering mobile games for Android / iOS
- Experienced in systems architecture and rapid prototyping
- Ability to work in a team environment and interface with all levels in the

#### Contact

+1 321 257 8668 redblame315@gmail.com

# Program Languages

- C/C++
- C#
- Java
- SQL
- Python
- JSON
- JS
- QT
- JSP
- Solidity

### **Education**

02/2009 to 03/2013, University of Toronto, Ontario

Bachelor of Computer Science